[{"answer": "We should be having dinner with our sons when we're sixty", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah, like I don't know that I'm pathetic", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah, like I don't know that I'm pathetic", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes. Me, too. I wanna be normal. Normal", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "So, then you asked yourselves,", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes. We did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "There isn't", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It's sad, my friend. It's a sad state of affairs.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh, you have no idea.", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You're what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh, my god! You're getting married", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What's the rope for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "The dog. You're getting the dog", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Did what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You're getting married", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm a man. my frien", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You're blown", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You stuck your hand out, so I shook it. I don't know about a pact. Anyway, you should be happy you're engaged. You're getting married", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You thought I was gonna get married", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What time you got", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What do you do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "How close do you get", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Tsk. Well, I can guess within the hour, and I don't even have to look at the sun", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Well, night's tougher but it's only a couple of hours", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah. Yeah. I'll know if he barks", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Bark", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "All right. Bark", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Bark.", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Get out!", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Engagement.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Arrest", "qsentId": 34}]